Contato

durvalino.ribeiro@hotmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/durvalino-ribeiro (LinkedIn)

Principais competências

Gestão hoteleira Hotelaria Gestão de hospitalidade

Certifications

Certificado de Competência Pedagógica

Durvalino Ribeiro

Business Development Manager na Wattosun Lisboa

Resumo

Business Manager with expertise in Hotel and Operations Management, responsible for the expansion of Grupo Fies in Portugal, a company of trendy bars and restaurants in Bairro Alto - Lisbon, participant on the opening of the iconic Hotel Atlantis de the Palm Jumeirah in Dubai in the Food & Beverages Department and the growth of Coconuts- Hotelaria e Turismo in Luanda leading the project of opening the Café del Mar beach club. Comfortable working on a multi-cultural, international work environment with experience on fast adapting operation procedures, management guidelines and everchanging realities in the Hotel and restaurant businesses.

Experiência

Wattosun
Business Development Manager
março de 2020 - Present (7 meses)
Lisboa, Portugal

Pestana Hotel Group MBA International Summer Project julho de 2019 - setembro de 2019 (3 meses) São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil

Coconuts - Hotelaria e turismo, Lda 6 anos 11 meses

Diretor Geral agosto de 2015 - junho de 2019 (3 anos 11 meses) Luanda - Angola

Gestor de Projeto agosto de 2012 - agosto de 2015 (3 anos 1 mês) Luanda

Desafio Gigante

Diretor Operacional julho de 2009 - outubro de 2011 (2 anos 4 meses) Organização de Eventos Gestão de Bares e discotecas

Atlantis The Palm
F&B Supervisor
setembro de 2008 - novembro de 2009 (1 ano 3 meses)
Dubai UAE

Eurostars Hotels Trainee de administração 2007 - 2007 (menos de um ano) Barcelona e Região, Espanha

Formação acadêmica

MIT Sloan School of Management Summer Immersion, MBA · (2019 - 2019)

The Lisbon MBA - Católica | Nova Master of Business Administration - MBA · (2019 - 2019)

Universidade do Algarve

Master's degree, Projetos de investimento na Hotelaria · (2012 - 2014)

Universidade do Algarve Licenciatura, Gestão Hoteleira · (2004 - 2008)